https://www.wool-underwear.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Checkout
Languages:    Currencies:
About Us
Welcome to our Store!
wool-underwear.com since 1999. Australian made supersoft fine merino wool thermal underwear .
Contact Us
Have a Question?
Your short message goes here.
Shipping
We airmail around the world..
Shop with Confidence
Paypal processes cards securely .
Contact Us
Currencies:
Singapore Dollar
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Privacy Policy: wool-underwear.com, collects only the information needed to ship goods and process credit card transactions using SSL(secure socket layer). During the purchase process, we will share your information with PayPal or the Commonwealth Bank of Australia, strictly to process your credit card transaction.
We use Paypal for secure PCI compliant credit card processing.
Comodo SSL Certificate has the
highest possible encryption levels for online transactions.Each certificate is signed with NIST recommended 2048 bit signatures and provides up to 256 bit encryption of customer data.
Cookies: wool-underwear.com shopping cart will use cookies to identify you during your session and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Cookies are never used to store sensitive customer information such as names, addresses, credit card numbers or passwords.
Automatic Information:We automatically track certain information. This information may include your IP address.
Advertisers: We work with third party advertising companies. These third parties may serve other cookies. These third parties use non-personally identifying information.
Third Party Sites: You may visit other web sites, through links on our site, who may collect, use and share information in accordance with their own privacy policies. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site, are not covered by this Policy.
Important Links
Customer Testimonials
Bestsellers
1.   221 Mens merino wool short sleeve ...
2.   231 MENS MERINO WOOL LONG JOHNS...
3.   291 MENS MERINO WOOL LONG SLEEVE...
4.   PBJ WOMENS MERINO WOOL LONG JOHNS
5.   211 MENS MERINO WOOL ATHLETIC...
6.   SP191 Mens Merino Skins Sports...
7.   PBSP WOMENS MERINO WOOL LONG...
8.   PBVM WOMENS MERINO WOOL TANK TOP...
9.   PBSM WOMENS MERINO WOOL LONG...
10.   231B MENS MERINO WOOL LONG JOHNS...
There currently are 4 guests online.
Quick LinksHomeFeatured ProductsSpecialsWhat's NewAll Products ...
InformationAbout UsSite MapGift Certificate FAQDiscount CouponsNewsletter Unsubscribe
Customer ServiceContact UsShipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseMy Account
Important Links Customer Testimonials
Copyright © 2020 wool-underwear.com.
Powered by Zen Cart.
Responsive Zen cart templates by Picaflor Azul.
